That's scary.
怖いね
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Sorry, all of a sudden.
ごめんね、急に
Stretch the wall.
壁伸ばしちゃって
Just a hobby.
ちょっと趣味で
You're scared.
怯えてるね
Don't be scared.
怯えないで
Because it's okay.
大丈夫だから
Because I don't do things like this.
こういうことしないから
Can I ask you a few questions?
ちょっと色々聞いてもいい?
How old are you now?
今何歳ある?
5 years old.
5歳
Whoa.
おっ
I'm back to school.
学校に帰ってんだ
Eh.
えー
What year are you in?
何年生なの?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだった
Fun school.
楽しい学校
Isn't it the end?
終わりなんじゃない?
Examination?
受験?
I'm studying for the exam.
受験勉強じゃん
very soon.
もうすぐ
What do you think?
どうなの?
Have you decided on your career path?
進路決めてるの?
picture?
え?
University.
大 学
All of a sudden, so casually.
急にね、こんな気軽で
That surprised me.
びっくりしたよね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
This is for hobby use.
これ趣味用なんだよ
University?
大学?
I'm studying.
勉強してるんだ
Are you thinking about what you want to study?
何を勉強したいとか考えてるの?
Science?
理系?
Humanities?
文系?
Humanities.
文系
The uniform looks good on you.
制服似合うね
copper?
どう?
this.
これ
The one I brought.
俺が持ってきたやつ
How about a regular uniform?
普段の制服と どう?
Are they similar?
似てる?
Ah, the same?
あ、同じ?
Does it feel the same?
同じ感じ?
Ah, like this.
あ、こんな
Check?
チェックの?
blazer?
ブレザー?
normally?
普段?
Socks?
靴下が?
socks?
靴下?
Something like this.
こういうの
Is it like this?
こういうのか
a little bit.
ちょっと
It smells nice.
いい香りするね
amazing.
すごい
It smells nice.
いい香りが
What shampoo do you use?
シャンプー何使ってるの?
this.
これ
That's right.
そうなんだ
picture?
え?
Oh, sorry.
あ、ごめんね
Do something bad.
悪いことして
Like this.
こんな
There's no reason for this.
わけないことなんだよ、これ
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトとかしてるの?
now.
今
A part-time job like this?
こういうバイト?
It's not this kind of part-time job.
こういうバイトじゃないよ
Ordinary part-time job?
普通のバイト?
Do you have a part-time job like this?
こういうバイトしてるの?
I haven't.
してない
My uncle will pay me a fair hourly wage today.
今日は、おじさんが ちゃんと 時給払うからね
Buy some delicious sweets.
美味 しいお菓子買ってね
My uncle says you shouldn't do this.
おじさん言うと こんなことしちゃダメだよ
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いるの?
now.
今
There is.
いる
Ah, there it is.
あ、いるんだ
Show me some photos.
ちょっと写真見せて
Is there someone you like?
好きな人いる?
boyfriend.
彼氏
I do naughty things like that with my boyfriend.
私、彼氏と そういうエッチなことをしてる
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうなんだ
nice.
いいね
It's youthful.
青春だね
Youth, or rather, the same school?
青春っていうか、 同じ学校?
boyfriend.
彼氏
That's right.
そうなんだ
Hey, I got it in a blink of an eye.
ちょ、 めくらくもらった
See you then.
じゃあね
Please give me a chew.
チューしてもらって
You have a boyfriend, right?
彼氏いるんでしょ?
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ?
What kind of chew do you want?
どんな、どんなチューする?
What kind of feeling?
どんな、ちょっと どんな感じで?
Oh, eh, don't be like this, this naughty.
あ、え、こんな こんな エッチみたいな チューじゃないで
Sho?
しょ?
No, right?
違う でしょ?
Isn't it a deeper feeling?
もっとディープな 感じじゃない?
picture?
え?
Really?
本当に?
You don't say "chew" when it comes to things like this, so I'll tell you.
こういうのは、チューって言わないから 教えてあげるから
Have your tongue stick out a little.
ちょっと舌、舌出してもらう
Tongue.
舌を
Oh, you look surprised.
あ、 びっくりした顔して
Were you surprised?
びっくりしたの?
Have you ever had a chew like this?
まさか こういうチューしたことない?
Isn't there?
ないの?
This is how you do it.
こう、こうやるんだよ
I'll tell you.
教えてあげるから
This is Babu Babu, isn't it?
これ、バブ バブでしょ、それは
Wait a minute, that's Babu.
ちょっと待って、それバブだって
No, I'll have you stick your tongue out.
違う、舌出してもらう
Tongue, stick out your tongue?
舌、舌を出すの?
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
What about bub?
バブは?
Oh, that's stupid, this.
あ、それバブだよ、これ
Babu, it's not Babu.
バブ、バブじゃないから
Stick out your tongue, say this, intertwine, yes.
舌を出して、こう、 絡め、そう
Why, why, why, why are you laughing like that?
なんで、なんで なんで、 なんでそんな笑うのさ
Hey, hey, just a second.
ちょ、ちょ、ちょっと
Ah, Bebe is here.
あ、ベベ来た
Eh, that's cute.
え、かわいい
Do you usually do this with your boyfriend?
普段、彼氏とこういうことしてるの?
That's it, that's it.
それよね、それ
Where are you doing it?
どこでしてるの?
It's easy to say, really.
いいやすいしてるね、ほんとね
Seduce your uncle.
おじさんを誘惑してね
Oh, I'm hiding it.
あ、隠してる
Babu.
バ ブ
Hey Babu, this.
ちょっとバブ、これ
Open your legs, Babu.
足開いてる、バブ
What is this?
なに、これ
I was thinking about something naughty.
エッチなこと考えてた
Ah, I hid it.
あ、隠した
feet.
足
Wow, that's amazing.
てか、すげえ
What is this?
なにこれ
What did you check just now?
なにを確認したの、今
Hehehe.
ふふふ
real.
ほんと
What is this, this underwear?
これなに、この下着
What is this?
なに、この
It's so cool.
すけすけ
This isn't too cool.
すけすぎじゃない、これ
You can see this.
見えてるじゃん、これ
What, do you always wear this to school?
え、いつも学校にこれで行くの?
Is this why you're going?
こういうので行くの?
Seriously?
マジで?
Kids these days are terrible.
最近の子やばいね
I'm buying this myself.
自分で買うの、これ
Ask your parents to buy it for you.
親に買ってもらう
Do you buy it yourself?
自分で買うの?
Awesome.
すげえ
It's broken,
割れてるもん、
here.
ここ
You must be really moody.
め っちゃムドウになってるでしょ
Touch it yourself.
触ってほら、自分で
Did you notice?
気づいた?
Don't babble yet, that.
まだバブタンするな、それ
I'll change the smell too.
匂いも変えておきますね
I haven't been wearing them all day today.
今日1日履いてたじゃないもんね
Just a little bit.
ちょっとさ、その
I have long legs.
足長い足でさ
Ah, this.
あ、これ
Isn't this going to come off?
これ、外れるんじゃない?
Maybe.
もしかして
From here.
こっから
picture?
え?
It doesn't come off.
外れない
I can't leave here.
ここ外れないんだ
fault.
あら
It's a little more dangerous.
もうちょっとやばい
with my own hands
自分の両手で
difference.
さ
It's really overflowing.
す っごい溢れてきてる
Let me open my legs.
足開いてもらおう
what happened?
どうしたの?
That's no good.
ダメだね
Why not?
なんでダメだよな
yeah?
ん?
Hmm, it's cute, monto.
うーん、かわいいよ、もんと
A little boyfriend.
ちょっと彼氏のとさ
Take a look and compare.
ちょっと見比べてみてよ
With my boyfriend.
彼氏のと
Let's go, Babtan.
行くよ、バブタン
Boyfriend, you’re also touching his position, right?
彼氏、彼氏の位置も触ってんでしょ?
That's amazing, the way you touch it.
すごいね、触り方
That's amazing.
すごいね
You're good at it, Ferrer.
上手だね、フェラーは
A little boyfriend.
ちょっと彼氏のとさ
Yeah.
うん
That's amazing.
すごいね
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
Lots of experiences.
体験がいっぱい
Oh no.
やば
It didn't come this far.
ここまで来なかった
You're doing really well.
すっごいペルペルしてるね
It didn't come this far.
ここまで来なかった
Is it okay?
いいかな?
Will I get scared?
おびれちゃうかな?
No.
ダメだよ
It's no good because it will come off.
外れちゃうから、ダメだよ
It will come off
外れちゃう
from.
から
Just put your feet up.
ちょっと 足をさ
Kakai.
かかい
Did you leave?
いっちゃったの?
Do it and put it on.
やるしにおんこして
Tight, tight.
きつい、きつい
What is that?
何それ?
Will you do it?
やってくれるの?
It's amazing that you've been doing this for so long.
こんな時間これをやって、すごいね
Are you coming here?
こっち来るの?
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
Can you move like that?
そんな動けるの?
Okay, let's do it.
いい よ、やっておこう
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
What is that?
何それ?
Will you do it?
やってくれるの?
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
It's amazing that you've been doing this for so long.
こんな時間これをやって、すごいね
good?
いい?
Okay, let's close it.
よし、閉じておこう
That's fine.
いいですよ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I also touched my feet.
足も手ついて
Open your legs.
足開いて
Let's slowly open our legs.
ゆっくり足開いておこう